W. R. "Bob" Poage Personal papers, Inclusive: 1766-2008, undated, Bulk: 1937-1978
Baylor University Libraries
- Biographical Materials, 1838-2008, undated; 1
  - Correspondence with The Texas Collection at Baylor University, 1970-1976 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1979 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Society of Supercitizens Saving Our Steamboat Delta Queen, Membership Certificate, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - “The Texas Farmer-Stockton”, “Who Will Write New Bill?”, 1970 January (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Top Op, “Showdown for Farm Programs”, 1970 January (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence and Surveys on Potato Hill Land, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - “Indian Tribal Areas” Map for “McLennan County — Before 1980”, circa 1971 (Box 123 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - “The Progressive Farmer,” Man of the Year, Certificate, 1971 January 1 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - National Limestone Institute, Distinguished Service Award, 1971 January 27 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Conger Poage, Letter on Helen C. Poage Expenses, 1971 March 4 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Temple, Texas Knights of Columbus, Resolution, 1971 October 11 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Scott A. Poage, Letter on Taxes, 1971 October 22 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Northwest Waco Lions Club, Certificate of Appreciation, 1971 December 29 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Robert Oliver, Letter on Loan Interest Payment, 1971 December 29 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Guest Book, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence on Sale of Interest in Tom’s Folly Farm, Clarksburg, Maryland, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Guest Book, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Guest Book, 1972-1975 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Law Alumni Association, Appointment as Counsellor to Baylor University School of Law, 1972 March 1 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence on Distinguished Citizen of Agriculture Honor, 1972 June (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Agriculture, Certificate, 1972 June 21 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - National Milk Producer’s Federation, Distinguished Citizen of Agriculture Award, 1972 June 21 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - “A Proposal for the Establishment of the W. R. Poage Congressional Library Center”, circa 1973 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence on Announcement of W. R. Poage Congressional Library Center, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Membership to U.S. Capitol Cornerstone Club, 1973 (Box 131 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Clippings on W. R. Poage Library Project, 1973-1976 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Publicity Materials for W. R. Poage Library, 1973-1979 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Masons of Texas, Certificate, 50-year Membership, 1973 January 15 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Honorary Oklahoman Citizenship Certification, 1973 April 13 (Box 131 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Rural Electrification Act, Financing Certificate, 1973 May 8 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Honorary Doctorate of Humanities Degree from University of Mary Hardin-Baylor, 1973 May 19 (Box 131 OVZ, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence among Poage Library Committee Members, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence on Donations to Poage Library Project, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Lists of Possible Contacts for Poage Library Development Board, circa 1974 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Admission for Portrait Ceremony of President Lyndon B. Johnson, 1974, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, Meetings Planning W. R. Poage Library, 1974-1976 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Correspondence on 1975 Hearne Bribe Scandal, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings on Local Celebrations for U.S. Bicentennial, 1974-1976 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Reported Recommendations of Community Service Board on W. R. Poage Congressional Library, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - “The American Legion Magazine”, “Should Congress Eliminate Farm Subsidy Payments?”, 1974 January (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Citation from National Association of Conservation Districts, 1974 February 12 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Rural Electrification, “REA Crisis to Energy Crisis”, 1974 April (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Guest Book for Brownwood Chamber of Commerce Event, 1974 April 4 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Guest List and Program for W. R. Poage Library Development Council Dinner, 1974 November 21 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence on Development of Library Project, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence on W. R. Poage Library Fundraising, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Donations and Accounting for W. R. Poage Library Project, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Guest Book, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Guest Book of Charles E. Blake, Office of Congressman W. R. Poage, 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Statements and Press Release on Tom Foley’s Appointment to Committee on Agriculture, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings on Agriculture Committee Ouster, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - W. R. Poage Library Progress Report, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Non-Commissioned Officers Association, Membership Certificate, 1975 June 25 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Joseph E. Johnston Camp, Certificate of Appreciation, 1975 August 21 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - National Alliance of Senior Citizens, Golden Age Hall of Fame Certificate, 1975 December 2 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Carpenter’s Legislation Improvement Committee, William Robert Poage Day, Resolution, 1975 December 22 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence on Development of W. R. Poage Library Project, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence on W. R. Poage Library Fundraising, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Guest Book, 1976-1978 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings on W. R. Poage Library Project, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Pledge List of W. R. Poage Library Donors, circa 1976 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - W. R. Poage Congressional Library Announcement, circa 1976 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - "They Grade the Congress", 1976 April (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - W. R. Poage Federal Building, Certificate and Flag, 1976 September 1 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Letter on Purchase of Congressional Desk, 1976 December (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Program for “W. R. Poage Day in Temple”, 1976 October 13 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Temple, Texas, Bob Poage Day, Proclamation, 1976 October 13 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Election Certificates, 1976 November 19 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence on Development of Library Project, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence on Purchase of Congressional Desk and Chair, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence on W. R. Poage Library Fundraising, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Report, and Schematics of W. R. Poage Library Center Ad Hoc Committee, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence with The Texas Collection at Baylor University, 1977-1979 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Articles on Poage’s Retirement, 1977-1979 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Poage Calendar, 1977 (Box 131 OVZ, Folder 29)
  - Trip Itinerary of Robbie Lee and Scott Poage, 1977 February (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Baylor University Heritage Club, Certificate, 1977 March 22 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - American Conservative Union Statesman Award, 1977 April 26 (Box 131 OVZ, Folder 30)
  - National Farmers Union, Green Thumbers Membership Certificate, 1977 August 24 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Letter from Jimmy Carter on Gifting Pen Used to Sign Legislation, 1977 October 19 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Program from Presentation of Animal Agriculture Award to Poage, 1977 November 7 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Biographies of Poage, 1978-2012 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Congressional Staff Club Certificate, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence on Frances C. Poage Map Room Donations, 1978-1981 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence on Retiring Waco Office, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence on Shipment of Items from Washington, D.C. to Waco, Texas, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Christmas Cards, 1978-1999, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Card Mailing List, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Guest Book, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - “In Tribute To... Mr. Agriculture” Program, circa 1978 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Guest Book for Bob Poage Appreciation Banquet, 1978 March 14 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - World of Agricultural Aviation, “Mr. Agriculture”, 1978 May (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - J. H. Hines Sixth Grade School, Certificate of Honor, 1978 May 30 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Southwestern Peanut Sheller’s Association, Certificate of Appreciation, 1978 June 27 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Baylor University Publication Packet, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Inventory of W. R. Poage Estate, 1979-1981 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Certificate of Membership to Caritas of Waco One Hundred Club, 1979 July (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - U. S. Department of Agriculture, Certificate of Appreciation, 1979 July 17 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - “The Pecan Quarterly”, “Texas Growers Honor Poage... Storey... Madden”, 1979 August (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Program for Dedication of W. R. Poage Legislative Library Center, 1979 September 21 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Accepted Invitations to Plaza Forum Organization, National Pork Producers Council, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Baylor Educator, “W. R. Poage Legislative Library Center”, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - “McLennan County-Before 1980,” Chapter 11 Correspondence and Research (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - “McLennan County-Before 1980,” Chapter 16 Correspondence and Research (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - “McLennan County-Before 1980,” Newspaper Clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - “McLennan County-Before 1980,” Sale Invoices, 1980-1983 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1980-1984 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1980 November-1981 March (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Executive Intelligence Review, “You Need to Get Things Done”, 1980 November 14 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, 1981 April-July (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Waco Association of Life Underwriters, Community Service Award, 1981 June 19 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, 1981 August-December (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence on Frances C. Poage Map Room, 1981 April (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - “McLennan County-Before 1980,” Printing Contract, 1981 May 13 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Texas House of Representatives Certificate of Honor, 1981 May 18 (Box 131 OVZ, Folder 31)
  - General Correspondence, 1982 January-March (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 1982 April-June (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, 1982 July-September (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, 1982 October-December (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - “Farm Bureau Honors Poage”, 1982 January 14 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - “How We Lived,” Correspondence on Photo Acquisition, 1983, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - “How We Lived,” Story and Illustration of The Beef Club, 1983 September 13 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - “How We Lived,” Contract with Davis Brothers Publishing Company, 1983 November 3 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - General Books and Documents of Scott T. Poage, 1984-1998 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Miss Nellie’s Pretty Place Announcement, circa 1984 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Signed Christmas Card from Poage, circa 1984 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - “The Senior’s Advisor”, “Older People Should Vote”, 1984 June (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Historic Waco Foundation, Inc., Certificate of Appreciation, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - “My First 85 Years”, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, Soil Conservation Service Award, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Texas State Technical Institute, Certificate of Appreciation, 1985 April 22 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Bartlett Electric Cooperative, Certificate of Appreciation, 1985 May 8 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Waco Independent School District, Citation, 1985 May 23 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence and Remarks on Boy Scouts Distinguished Man of the Year Award, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Get Well Soon and Christmas Cards, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - “My First 85 Years,” Correspondence, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Last Will of W. R. Poage, Filed in McLennan County, Texas 14 January 1987, 1986 June 12 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Boy Scouts of America Program for Distinguished Citizen Award, 1986 June 26 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - “Poage Park Dedication Set Sunday at Woodway”, 1986 July 23 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Woodway, Texas, Bob Poage Day Proclamation, 1986 July 27 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Dedication of Miss Nellie’s Pretty Place, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper Clippings on Death of W. R. Poage, 1987, undated (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Republic Bank of Waco, Resolution Honoring the Memory of W. R. Poage, 1987 January 13-21 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Waco Chamber of Commerce, Resolution Honoring the Memory of W. R. Poage, 1987 February 11 (Box 131 OVZ, Folder 32)
  - Ronald Reagan, Certificate Honoring W. R. Poage Military Service, 1987 March (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Letters Confirming Donations to Miss Nellie’s Pretty Place in honor of Poage, 1987 April-December (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Resolution by Republic Bank of Waco Honoring Poage, circa 1987 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - “Baylor Scott & White Quarterly”, “In Memoriam...”, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - “The Legacy of Mr. Agriculture,” “Waco Tribune-Herald”, 1999 December 29 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Draft, Fowler West, “Glimpses into My Years with Congressman Bob Poage”, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Scott T. Poage Obituary, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Poage Portrait Presentation, Preparations and Invitation Responses, Correspondence and Checklists, 1968 February (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Robert F. Kennedy, Response to Endorsement Request, Letter, 1968 March 20 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Letter about W. R. Poage Traffic Ticket, 1972 November 3 (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Law Practice, 1924-1938, undated; 2
  This series contains mostly personal correspondence between W. R. Poage and his clients, with relevant notes, legal documents, and financial records. Poage’s law office was in the Amicable (ALICO) Building, where he practiced law with Pat M. Neff, Jr. The documents in this series show his work with clients on collections, land and mineral leases, logistics companies, and probate law. The folders are arranged alphabetically by name and are in good condition.
  - “Ada Wynne Matthews v. Floyd Milton Matthews,” Divorce, Correspondence, 1934 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - A.E. Morrison and J.W. Morrison, Vendor’s Lien Notes, 1917-1927 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - “A.L. Frizzell v. J.C. Houser,” Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1931-1932 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Allen, Mrs. Maude P. and L.S. Wright, Note Due, Correspondence, 1933-1935 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - “Angeline Thomas v. Henry Thomas” and “Rotan Mims v. Angeline Thomas,” Correspondence and Notices, 1933-1934 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Legal Documents, 1934 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Assorted Legal Documents, 1935-1936 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Assorted Wills, 1924-1937 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Atascosa County and Frio County, Oil Leases, Correspondence, 1936 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Barnett Brothers, Burks & Son Common Carrier Certificate, Correspondence, 1933-1935 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Bateman, Wayne, Life Insurance, Correspondence, 1934 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Beatty, Mrs. Royal, R.M. Phillips Estate, Correspondence, 1936 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Bills and Statements, 1931-1935 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - “Bobby Fuller v. Gulf Oil Company,” Correspondence and Briefs, 1936 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Bowman, Newton H., “City of Waco v. Dan LeBow Sr., et al,” Tax Suit, Correspondence, 1932 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Brady Freight Lines, Correspondence, 1935 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Bushong Family Land, “Bessie I. Nininger v. David A. Bushong,” Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1933-1934 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Bushong Family Land, “C.A. Hering v. L.C. Bushong,” Correspondence, 1934 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Bushong Family Land, Kime & Kime Correspondence, 1934-1936 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Bushong Family Land, Lyle C. Bushong Land Sale, Correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Bushong Family Land, “Lyle C. Bushong v. David A. Bushong,” Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1934-1936 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Bushong Family Land, Will and Estate of Maggie C. Bushong, Legal Documents, Map, and Correspondence, 1934 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - “C.A. Duren v. M. Hoffman,” Legal Documents and Correspondence, 1932-1936 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Carroll Minors, Correspondence, 1930 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Carroll Minors, Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1931-1932 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Carroll Minors, Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1933-1934 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Carroll Minors, Discharge of Rupert and Alfred Carroll, Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1934-1935 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Carroll Minors, Hight, Clay, Transfer of Guardianship, Legal Documents, 1929 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Carroll Minors, Legal Documents, undated (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Carroll Minors, “Mrs. Eunice Carroll Thompson v. Sweeney & Co.,” Car Accident Claim, Correspondence, 1935 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Carroll Minors, Rupert Carroll Admission to Austin State School, Lunacy Case, Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1934-1935 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Central Forwarding, Correspondence, 1929 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Central Freight Lines, Accident Claims, Correspondence, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Central Freight Lines, “A.F. Decker v. Charles Krugman, et al,” Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Central Freight Lines, Applications 1120 and 1143, Correspondence, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Central Freight Lines, “Armour & Co. v. Central Freight Lines,” Correspondence, 1930-1931 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Central Freight Lines, “Austin National Bank v. E.D. Balcom, et al,” Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Central Freight Lines, Certificates, Correspondence, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Central Freight Lines, Certificate, Temple to Brenham, Correspondence, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Central Freight Lines, General Correspondence, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Central Freight Lines, General Correspondence, 1931-1932 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Central Freight Lines, General Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Central Freight Lines, General Correspondence and Route Schedules, 1935-1937, undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Central Freight Lines, “G & H Freight v. Central Freight Lines,” Correspondence, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Central Freight Lines, Graham, O.D. and Reeves, J.P., Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Central Freight Lines, Inter City Forwarding, Correspondence, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Central Freight Lines, “J.C. Dorbandt v. Central Freight Lines,” Correspondence, 1931 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - “Central Freight Lines v. L.G. Phares, et al,” Legal Documents, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Central Freight Lines, L. S. & P. Freight Lines Claims, Correspondence, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Central Freight Lines Luedecke, W.G., Notes Due, Correspondence, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Central Freight Lines, Milam County Motor Carrier Application, Correspondence, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Central Freight Lines, “Monroe Horn v. Central Freight Lines,” Correspondence, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Central Freight Lines, Railroad Commission, Correspondence, 1931-1932 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Central Freight Lines Red Arrow Freight, Correspondence, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Central Freight Lines, Red Arrow Freight, English Freight Company Accident, Correspondence, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Central Freight Lines, Ruby Motor Freight, Correspondence, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Central Freight Lines, Southwest Motor Freight Lines Application, Correspondence, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Central Freight Lines, Temple Candy Company, Correspondence, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Central Freight Lines, Texas Company Accident Claim, Correspondence, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Central Freight Lines, Union Truck Lines, A.H. Seibert, Correspondence and Circulars, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Central Texas Broadcasting Company, W.A.C.O. Radio, Advertising Contracts, Contracts, Correspondence and Notice, 1931-1934 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Clarkson Family Oil and Gas Rights, Correspondence, 1936 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - “C.L. Bryant v. Bob Hinson, et al,” Correspondence, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - “Club Café v. Mrs. J.L. Myers,” Correspondence and Checks, 1930, 1933 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - “C.N. Taylor v. W.E. Taylor, et al,” Legal Documents, Correspondence, 1929-1933 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Collier Family and Raglin H. Jones, Correspondence, 1930-1934 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Commercial Credit Company, Byrne, J.H., Byrne Kelvinator Company, Correspondence, 1931-1933 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Commercial Credit Company, Byrne, J.H., Debt Collection, Correspondence, 1933-1936 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Commercial Credit Company, Debt Collection, Correspondence, 1932-1933 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Commercial Credit Company, Frank Youree Bankruptcy, Baseball Lighting Equipment, Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - “Commercial Credit Company v. O.E. Moore,” Correspondence, 1932-1935 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Commercial Credit Company, Lewis, D.D., Correspondence, 1932-1933 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Common Carrier, Motor Carrier, Circulars, 1930-1931 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Common Carrier, Motor Carrier, Circulars, 1932 January-March (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Common Carrier, Motor Carrier, Circulars, 1932 April-June (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Common Carrier, Motor Carrier, Circulars, 1932 July-September (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Common Carrier, Motor Carrier, Circulars, 1932 October-December (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Common Carrier, Motor Carrier, Circulars, 1933 January-March (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Common Carrier, Motor Carrier, Circulars, 1933 April-June (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Common Carrier, Motor Carrier, Circulars, 1933 July (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Common Carrier, Motor Carrier, Circulars, 1933 August-September (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Common Carrier, Motor Carrier, Circulars, 1933 October-December (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Conger Family, Notes Due, Correspondence, 1931-1934 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Conger, J.D. and Hamilton, Mrs. D.C., Notes Due, Correspondence, 1933 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Conger, J.D., Mineral Wells Property, Correspondence, 1930-1936 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Conley, Charles A., Findlay Drilling Corporation, Correspondence and Financial Documents, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence on Land in Comanche County, Texas, 1933-1936 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence on Rental of Bartlett, Texas House, 1931-1933 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Cottingham, Claybrook and Hamilton, Ruth, Correspondence, 1934-1936 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Crosthwait, W.L., Injury Insurance Claim, Correspondence, 1930-1932 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Crown, Henry, Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Custody and Estate of William E. Peters, Jr., Correspondence and Notices, 1926-1938 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - “David Brothers Publishing Company v. Lutterloh,” Correspondence, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - “Duke Martin V. Helen C. Poage,” Correspondence, 1932 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - “E.A. Starling v. Bertha Starling,” Correspondence, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - “E.I. Brewster v. John Dollins,” Correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Estate of E. Manuel Hatwoff, Will and Contracts, 1931-1935 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Estate of Joseph Jansa, Sr., Correspondence and Financial Documents, 1934-1938 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Estate of Silas Brittin Edens, Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1933-1934 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - “Eva Gibson v. Dennis & Boykins Undertaking” and “Fannie Busby v. Dennis & Boykins Undertaking,” Legal Documents, 1933 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Fall, Mary E., Correspondence, 1927-1934 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - “Farm and Home v. W.O. Hastings, et al,” Correspondence and Legal Documents, 1934-1936 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Federal Communications Commission, T.E. Kirksey, Docket, 1937 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - “A.L. Hatch v. W.S. Foster,” Legal Documents, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Foster, W.S., Central Texas Publishing Co., Correspondence, 1929 (Box 40, Folder 17)